[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
[straw squeaking]
[吸管吱吱声]
[straws squeaking]
- Stop it!
别闹了！
Stop making such immature noises.
别发出这么幼稚的声音。
[trumpet fanfare]
[号角声]
- Hear ye! Hear ye!
听好了！听好了！
Ye Olde Tom's Get Sporty!
老汤姆的运动会！
would like to invite one and all
诚邀各位
to the Tenth Annual Renaissance Faire.
参加第十届文艺复兴博览会。
As King and Queen... - Hello.
作为国王和王后... - 你好。
- We shall rule thy fairgrounds with our loyal, royal dragon...
- 我们将与我们的忠诚皇家龙一起统治这片集市...
Squishy Puffs.
软绵绵。
- [barks]
- [吠叫]
all: Aww.
所有人: 哎呀。
- Ah, the Ren Faire, where we can eat with our hands,
- 啊，这个文艺复兴集市，我们可以用手吃东西，
scratch whatever itches, and burp at will.
挠任何痒的地方，还可以随意打嗝。
- Come on, let's practice.
- 来吧，让我们练习一下。
Dawn, you be will.
黎明，你来打嗝。
[all belch] - [chuckles]
[所有人打嗝] - [轻笑]
- Stop it!
别闹了！
You guys are gonna ruin the Ren Faire for me.
你们这样会毁了我对Ren Faire的印象。
Why can't I just go with somebody more mature?
为什么我就不能和更成熟的人一起去呢？
- [gasps]
（惊讶声）
Who could possibly be more mature than us?
还有谁能比我们更成熟呢？
- Someone like Mack.
比如Mack。
- That's pretty mature.
那确实挺成熟的。
- In fact, I'm gonna go ask Mack
实际上，我要去邀请Mack
to go to the Ren Faire with me, and show you guys
和我一起去Ren Faire，让你们看看
how mature people hang out together.
成熟的人是怎么一起出去玩的。
- A date, huh? [both scream]
约会，嗯？[两人尖叫]
- You let Dooley know if you need anything.
如果你需要什么，告诉Dooley。
Say, a new outfit, some lip gloss...
比如，一套新衣服，一些唇彩...
- It's not a date, Dooley.
这不是约会，Dooley。
Mack and I hang out together all the time.
Mack和我经常一起出去。
We've been to the movies, a dance, lunch as friends.
我们一起去过电影院，参加过舞会，作为朋友一起吃过午饭。
- [scoffs] Child's play.
哼，小孩子的游戏。
Those are all two hours, max. But the Ren Faire?
那些最多两小时。但Ren Faire呢？
We're talking an all-day commitment.
我们说的是一整天的承诺。
- What's wrong, Dawn? Not mature enough for a date?
怎么了，Dawn？约会对你来说还不够成熟吗？
- Please. "Mature" is my middle name.
拜托，“成熟”可是我的中间名。
- I'm pretty sure it's Abigail.
我很确定是Abigail。
- It is?
是吗？
Wait, then whose middle name is Steven?
等等，那谁的中间名是Steven？
- Yours.
你的。
- Uh, pretty sure mine's Abigail.
呃，我很确定我的中间名是Abigail。
- Steven!
Steven！
- While you three bicker,
当你们三个争吵时，
the mature Quad has a social engagement to arrange.
成熟的Quad有社交活动要安排。
- [scoffs]
哼！
- Yeah, it's Abigail.
是的，是阿比盖尔。
- Hey, Mack, do you wanna go on a date with me
嘿，Mack，你想和我一起去文艺复兴博览会约会吗？
to the Renaissance Faire?
是的。
- Yeah. - Great!
太好了！
Hear ye! Hear ye! In ye faces.
听好了！听好了！就在你们面前。
Mae, will you join me at the luncheon counter?
Mae，你能和我一起去午餐柜台吗？
- [sighs] I can't believe she's going on a date.
（叹气）我真不敢相信她要去约会。
- I can't believe I'm going on a date.
我真不敢相信我要去约会。
- She's not mature enough for a date.
她还没有成熟到可以约会。
- I'm not mature enough for a date.
我还没有成熟到可以约会。
- As much as I'd hate to admit it,
尽管我讨厌承认，
maybe Dawn is more mature than us.
也许Dawn比我们更成熟。
- But we're Quads.
但我们可是四胞胎。
We go through everything together.
我们经历一切都在一起。
Learning to walk; learning to ride bikes;
学走路；学骑自行车；
learning long division.
学长除法。
- Yeah, long division.
对，长除法。
- Yeah, riding bikes.
对，骑自行车。
- You have to come with me. - [scoffs]
你得跟我一起去。
I don't wanna be the third wheel.
我不想当电灯泡。
- Oh, hey, Miles. May wants to know
哦，嘿，迈尔斯。梅想知道
if you wanna go on a date with her to the Renaissance Faire.
你是否愿意和她一起去文艺复兴博览会约会。
- Really? You do?
真的吗？你愿意吗？
- I do? - You do.
我愿意吗？- 你愿意。
- I do! I--I mean, only if you want--
我愿意！我——我是说，只要你愿意——
- I do. - Oh, cool.
我愿意。- 哦，太好了。
- Cool. - Cool.
太好了。- 太好了。
- Cool.
太好了。
Hey, guys. Dawn just got me a date with Mae.
嘿，伙计们。 Dawn刚刚帮我约了Mae。
Yes!
太棒了！
- Now she's getting dates for other people?
- 现在她还能帮别人安排约会？
We gotta get dates.
我们得找人约会。
- Maybe we should get Dawn to get us dates.
- 也许我们应该让Dawn帮我们安排约会。
- No, we've gotta get our own dates.
- 不，我们得自己找约会对象。
- I don't know, she seems pretty good at it.
- 我不知道，她看起来很擅长这个。
- Yeah, and I'm sure she wouldn't mind helping us.
- 是啊，我肯定她不会介意帮我们的。
I mean, she holds me up when I ride a bike...
我的意思是，我骑自行车的时候她会扶着我...
for some reason.
出于某种原因。
- We are getting our own dates!
- 我们要自己找约会对象！
And you're learning how to ride a bike!
而且你要学会骑自行车！
- I know how to ride a bike.
- 我会骑自行车。
Will you hold me like Dawn?
你会像Dawn那样扶着我吗？
[upbeat music]
[欢快音乐]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪ - ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 一，二 ♪ - ♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
- ♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪ - ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪♪
- [wincing]
- [皱眉]
- Do you have to limp so loudly?
- 你非得跛得这么大声吗？
- Did you have to teach me how to ride a bike
- 在我们约女生出去之前，你非得教我怎么骑自行车吗？
before we asked the girls out?
- I thought it would give us confidence heading into this.
- 我以为这会让我们更有信心面对这件事。
- And it worked. I feel really good about myself.
- 确实有效。我对自己感觉很好。
- All right, there they are.
- 好了，她们在那儿。
- [sighs] - Let's do this.
- [叹气] - 我们开始吧。
- Hello, ladies.
- 嗨，女士们。
- What's the haps?
- 有什么新鲜事吗？
- Would you girls wanna go on a date with us
你们女生愿意和我们一起去参加Ren Faire吗？
to the Ren Faire?
为什么不去呢？
all: Why not?
那些男生在搞什么鬼？
- What are those boys up to?
我不知道，但看起来不怎么样。
- I don't know, but it doesn't look cool.
猜猜谁刚刚登上了前往成熟岛的下一班船？
- Guess who just boarded the next boat to mature island?
我们刚刚邀请了Olivia、Avery和June
- We just asked Olivia, Avery, and June
作为我们的约会对象去Faire。
to go to the Faire as our dates.
他们说，“为什么不呢？”
- And they said, "Why not?"
我知道你们在打什么主意。
- I know what you're up to.
打什么主意？我们只是在表现成熟。
- Up to? We're just being mature.
- 意图？我们只是在展现成熟。
- It sounds like your slow boat is following my jet plane.
- 听起来你的慢船正跟着我的喷气式飞机。
But I guess that makes sense,
但我想这说得通，
because girls do mature faster than boys.
因为女孩确实比男孩成熟得快。
- Oh, yeah? Care to prove it?
- 哦，是吗？敢证明一下吗？
- I don't have anything to prove to you.
- 我没什么需要向你证明的。
- Oh, yeah? Prove that.
- 哦，是吗？证明这一点。
- Nothing is getting proven, except how immature you all are.
- 没什么被证明，除了你们有多不成熟。
- Since we maturely disagree,
- 既然我们成熟地意见不合，
why don't we settle this with a little mature-off?
为什么不通过一个小小的成熟比赛来解决呢？
- Yeah. both: A mature-off!
是的，一个成熟度比拼！
- I'd accept your challenge, and I'd win,
我会接受你的挑战，并且我会赢，
but lucky for you, there's no such thing as a mature-off.
但幸运的是，没有所谓的成熟度比拼。
- A mature-off, huh? [all scream]
成熟度比拼，嗯？[所有人尖叫]
- Oh, there's such a thing.
哦，确实有这种事。
- This should be good.
这应该会很有趣。
- Getting a date is easy,
约会是容易的，
but the mark of true maturity is making a connection.
但真正成熟的标志是建立联系。
- What kind of connection?
什么样的联系？
- Mind, body, soul.
心灵、身体、灵魂。
The triangle of romance. all: Whoa.
浪漫三角。大家：哇。
- No.
- 不。
- Hey, I don't make this stuff up.
- 嘿，我可不是编的。
- I think you do.
- 我觉得你是。
- First, you must connect the mind,
- 首先，你必须连接心灵，
which you'll do through simple conversation.
- 通过简单的对话来实现。
- Mack and I talk all the time.
- 我和Mack经常聊天。
- Next, the body, a connection by holding hands,
- 其次，身体，通过牵手来连接，
fingers intertwined.
- 手指交缠。
- We have hands. - [whispers] Whoo.
- 我们有手。- [低语] 哇。
- And third, while holding hands,
- 第三，在牵手的同时，
you must look deeply into each other's eyes,
你们必须深情地凝视对方的眼睛，
thus connecting your souls.
以此连接你们的灵魂。
- We have souls.
- 我们有灵魂。
- On both feet.
- 在两只脚上。
- But how do you know so much about romance?
- 但你怎么知道这么多关于浪漫的事情？
- He doesn't.
- 他不知道。
- She's right. I don't.
- 她说得对。我不知道。
But my sister does.
但我妹妹知道。
She's in high school.
她在上高中。
all: Oh!
哦！
- So?
所以呢？
- And she has a boyfriend.
而且她有个男朋友。
all: Whoa.
哇。
- No.
不。
- And he drives.
而且他会开车。
all: What?
什么？
- Ever.
从来。
- So now that we know the rules,
既然我们现在知道了规则，
do any of you boys think you have what it takes
你们这些男孩中，有谁认为自己具备完成这个浪漫三角的条件吗？
to complete the triangle of romance?
完成浪漫三角吗？
I know I do.
我知道我能。
Aw, what's wrong?
哦，怎么了？
Your little toy boat running out of gas?
你的小玩具船没油了？
- No. - We're in.
- 不是。 - 我们加入。
- And we're full of gas.
- 而且我们油箱满满的。
[all laugh]
[大家都笑了]
- Okay.
- 好吧。
Let the mature-off begin.
成熟比赛开始。
♪ ♪
[lively flute music]
[trumpet fanfare]
[小号齐鸣]
- Welcome, lords and ladies, to the Renaissance Faire.
- 欢迎，各位贵族，来到文艺复兴市集。
- Let us explore our kingdom.
- 让我们探索我们的王国。
- Indeed.
- 确实。
- Look at all this old-timey food.
- 看看这些古老时代的食物。
Turkey legs, beef ribs, pork chop on a stick?
火鸡腿，牛肋排，猪排串？
- Wow, that's a lot of portable meat.
- 哇，这么多便携的肉类。
[poof!] - Whoa.
[嘭！] - 哇。
- [coughing]
- [咳嗽声]
Harpers, come hither over yonder.
哈珀斯，来这边。
- Are we hithering or yondering?
- 我们是来这边还是去那边？
- Just come here.
- 就过来这里。
- Excuse us while we hither over yonder.
- 请原谅我们，我们要去那边。
- All right, remember,
- 好吧，记住，
the all-seeing Dooley the Great will be watching
无所不见的杜利大师将会观察
for whoever completes the triangle of romance first.
谁先完成浪漫三角。
- How will you watch us all at the same time?
- 你怎么能同时看到我们所有人？
- Yeah.
- 是啊。
- Pshoo! [poof!]
- 噗！[消失声！]
- How is he gonna watch us if he's not here?
- 如果他不在这里，他怎么监视我们？
- Oh, I'm here. [all scream]
- 哦，我在这里。[大家尖叫]
- But now I'm not. Whoosh!
- 但现在我不在了。呼！
- So what do you guys wanna do first?
- 那你们想先做什么？
- I wanna catapult a watermelon.
- 我想用弹弓发射一个西瓜。
- I wanna try a turkey leg.
- 我想试试火鸡腿。
♪ ♪
- That's it! Hand-holding, here I come.
- 就是这样！我要开始牵手了。
Huh. I guess that's the way you walk at a Renaissance Faire.
- 嗯，我想这就是在文艺复兴博览会上走路的方式。
Maybe we should walk like that.
也许我们应该那样走路。
♪ ♪
- Okay.
好的。
♪ ♪
- Wanna get some portable meat? - Thought you'd never ask.
想吃点便携的肉吗？——我还以为你永远不会问呢。
- Well, we're gonna be over by the ring toss.
好吧，我们会在套环游戏那边。
- Meet us there.
在那儿见。
- Let's end this. I'm going in, boys.
让我们结束这一切。我要进去了，伙计们。
- How are you gonna do it? - I'm going to woo milady
你打算怎么做？——我要用当时的语言去打动那位女士。看着——学着点。
with the language of the day. Watch-eth and learn-eth.
我亲爱的女士是否愿意与我交谈，或许还愿意握住我的手？
Doth my fair maiden want-eth to talk-eth
我的美丽佳人是否愿意与我交谈，
and hold-eth my hand-eth perhaps-eth?
或许还愿意握住我的手？
- Why are you talking so weird?
- 你为什么说话这么奇怪？
- [sighs] He crash-eth and burn-eth.
- [叹气] 他搞砸了。
- Meat! Hot meat here!
- 肉！热腾腾的肉在这里！
- Don't worry. I got this.
- 别担心，我搞得定。
The way to a woman's soul is through her stomach.
通往女人灵魂的路是通过她的胃。
Let me have one of your finest turkey legs.
给我来一只你们最好的火鸡腿。
- That will be $12.
- 那要12美元。
- Let me have one of your less fine turkey legs.
- 给我来一只没那么好的火鸡腿。
- $11. - Oh, ew, greasy.
-$11. - 哦，呃，油腻的。
Uh, can I have a napkin?
呃，能给我一张餐巾纸吗？
- Yep, $2. - Wha--
- 是的，$2。 - 什么--
they're free with the $12 legs.
它们是和$12的腿一起免费的。
- It doesn't seem like such a bad deal now, does it?
- 现在看起来不那么糟糕了，对吧？
- Ooh, a turkey leg. Can I have some?
- 哦，一个火鸡腿。我可以吃一些吗？
- Yes, I bought it for thee.
- 是的，我为你买的。
- [sighs] Should've bought a napkin.
- [叹气] 应该买张餐巾纸的。
But don't worry. Sir Dicky to the rescue.
但别担心。迪基先生来救场了。
Hey, June, why don't you come sit
嘿，琼，你为什么不坐到那张浪漫的椅子上来？
on that romantic chair with me?
坐在那张浪漫的椅子上和我一起吗？
- Dicky, that's not a romantic chair.
- 迪基，那不是一张浪漫的椅子。
That's a catapult.
那是一架弹射器。
- Well, it would be romantic if you sat--
- 嗯，如果你坐上去的话，就会变得浪漫——
[wailing] Here!
[哀嚎] 这里！
- Okay, just going to take her hand...
好吧，就牵着她的手...
Yes! Now, interlock fingers, and...
是的！现在，手指交缠，然后...
- Yes! Wow, she's not letting go.
- 是的！哇，她不肯放手。
- Now all I need to do is make eye contact.
- 现在我只需要...进行眼神交流。
- Well, I gotta go to the little m'ladies room.
- 嗯，我得去一下小女士的洗手间。
- Me too.
- 我也是。
both: Why am I still holding her hand?
两人：为什么我还在握着她的手？
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
- Ah! [both scream]
- 啊！[两人尖叫]
- Guys, I flew over Dawn near the palm reader.
- 伙计们，我在算命摊附近看到了Dawn。
She's getting close to beating us.
她快要超过我们了。
We gotta do something.
我们得做点什么。
Also, you gotta try the catapult.
还有，你得试试那个弹射器。
It's awesome.
太棒了。
- I can't wait to get my fortune told.
- 我迫不及待想算命了。
- I can't waste time on this long line.
我不能在这长队上浪费时间。
I've got a hand to hold.
我得抓紧时间。
Wait, that's it.
等等，就是这样。
Why wait? I can read your palm myself.
为什么要等？我可以自己看你的手相。
- You know how to read palms? - Of course.
- 你会看手相吗？ - 当然会。
I read 'em left and right. [laughs]
我左右手都能看。[笑]
Now I just need to look into your eyes.
现在我只需要看看你的眼睛。
- Aren't you supposed to look into my palm?
- 你不是应该看我的手掌吗？
- Hey, which one of us went to Camp Wanna-read-a-palm-a?
- 嘿，我们俩谁去过Camp Wanna-read-a-palm-a？
- You? - I saw that you would say that.
- 你？ - 我就知道你会这么说。
- So... [laughs] what else do you see?
- 那么... [笑] 你还看到了什么？
- Victory. - Look out
- 胜利。 - 小心
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- Ugh, that was close.
- 呃，好险。
Good thing you didn't spring for the napkins.
幸好你没买餐巾纸。
- We've gotta find a way to put some distance
- 我们得想办法拉开
between Dawn and Mack's greasy hands.
晨和麦克的油腻之手之间的距离。
- Hey, Mack. Milord; m'buddy; m'pal.
- 嘿，麦克。大人；我的哥们；我的朋友。
- How are things going with you and m'sister?
- 你和我妹妹相处得怎么样？
- Good, I think.
- 不错，我觉得。
- Well, if you wanna impress Dawn,
- 嗯，如果你想给Dawn留下深刻印象，
you should know that Dawn loves fairy tales.
你应该知道Dawn喜欢童话故事。
- Oh, yeah. Dawn loves that stuff.
- 哦，是的。Dawn喜欢那些东西。
Her middle name is "Fairy-tale."
她的中间名就是“童话”。
- Yup, Dawn Abigail Steven Mature Fairy-tale Harper.
- 没错，Dawn Abigail Steven Mature 童话 Harper。
- Mine's Albert.
- 我的中间名是Albert。
- Your name's not really important.
- 你的名字其实不重要。
What is important is that Dawn has always wished
重要的是Dawn一直希望
for a knight in shining armor.
能遇到一个身披闪亮盔甲的骑士。
- Of course, Dawn will want to test you
- 当然，Dawn会想要考验你
to make sure you're a true knight,
以确保你是一位真正的骑士，
and a true knight is never seen without his armor on.
而真正的骑士从不脱下他的盔甲。
- Especially the gloves. Don't ever take the gloves off.
- 尤其是手套。永远不要脱下手套。
Do you understand, Mack Albert?
你明白了吗，麦克·阿尔伯特？
- Yeah, it's pretty straightforward.
- 是的，这很简单明了。
- Okay, that'll delay Dawn,
- 好的，这会拖延到道恩，
but now one of us has to complete the triangle.
但现在我们中的一个必须完成这个三角。
- We gotta get back to the girls.
- 我们得回到女孩们那里。
- I know a shortcut.
- 我知道一条捷径。
- [all screaming]
- [所有人尖叫]
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
all: M'ladies. - [groans]
所有人: 女士们。 - [呻吟]
- Wait, where's Mack? - Hey, Dawn.
- 等等，Mack在哪儿？ - 嘿，Dawn。
- Mack? - Ah, dude, shiny.
- Mack？ - 啊，伙计，真亮。
- I'm like something out of a fairy tale, right?
- 我就像童话故事里走出来的一样，对吧？
- Aren't you hot in there? - A little.
- 你不热吗？ - 有点。
- Okay, that looks really uncomfortable.
- 好吧，那看起来真的很不舒服。
Maybe you should take it off.
也许你应该脱掉它。
- A true knight must stay-eth in his armor,
- 真正的骑士必须留在他的盔甲里，
lest his lady need-eth protection.
以免他的女士需要保护。
Especially the gloves. But you'd know that,
尤其是手套。但你会知道的，
Dawn Abigail Steven Mature Fairy-tale Harper.
Dawn Abigail Steven Mature Fairy-tale Harper。
- I think the heat is getting to him.
- 我觉得是热气让他有点晕了。
- No, I think my brothers got to him.
- 不，我觉得是我兄弟们搞的鬼。
- Little bit of both.
- 两者都有一点。
[loud crash]
（大声的撞击声）
- In the future, we may all travel by catapult.
- 未来，我们可能都得靠弹射器旅行了。
all: Ooh.
众人：哦。
- Care to step into the future with me?
- 愿意和我一起迈向未来吗？
Hey, Mack Albert, I'm working here.
嘿，Mack Albert，我正在工作呢。
- But I see you still have your gloves on
- 但我看到你还是戴着我们让你戴的手套。
like we told you to.
就像我们告诉你的那样。
- I knew you three were up to something.
- 我就知道你们三个在搞什么鬼。
- Wow. She's steaming mad.
- 哇。她气得冒烟了。
- Uh, excuse us for a moment.
- 呃，请让我们离开一会儿。
- I cannot believe you guys tried to ruined my date
- 我真不敢相信你们竟然试图破坏我的约会，
by using my love of fairy tales against me.
利用我对童话的热爱来对付我。
- Sorry, Dawn. Sometimes the Ren Faire
- 对不起，Dawn。有时候，
is a little unfair. [laughs] Nailed it.
中世纪市集有点不公平。[笑] 说中了。
- Hark, ye subjects!
- 听好了，臣民们！
'Tis time to get jousty.
是时候开始比武了。
[laughs]
[笑]
The winners shall be crowned Lord or Lady of the Faire.
获胜者将被加冕为市集的领主或女士。
- And with their partners,
- 并且与他们的伴侣一起，
they will join the Royal Procession,
他们将加入皇家游行，
holding hands thusly.
这样手牵手。
[swooning sigh]
[陶醉的叹息]
- That's it. If we win the joust,
- 就是这样。如果我们赢得比武，
we can hold hands thusly,
我们就可以这样手牵手，
and thus complete the triangle of romance.
从而完成浪漫的三角关系。
- Wait, do you think holding hands thusly counts?
- 等等，你觉得这样牵手算数吗？
- I'll allow it. [all scream]
- 我允许。[大家尖叫]
- Poof!
- 消失！
I'm just gonna walk off.
我这就走开。
I'm out of pellets.
我的弹丸用完了。
- All right, so let's settle this with a joust.
- 好吧，那我们就用比武来解决吧。
- Joust we shall.
- 比武就比武。
- So how's your balance in that armor?
- 你穿那身盔甲平衡感怎么样？
- Not great. Why?
- 不太好。怎么了？
[loud crash]
[巨大的撞击声]
- To the catapult!
向投石器前进！
[all screaming]
所有人尖叫
- We're getting good at this.
我们越来越擅长这个了。
- Okay, Dicky, focus.
好吧，迪基，集中注意力。
How are we gonna win the joust against all these people?
我们怎么能在这么多人面前赢得马上比武呢？
- I've got an idea.
我有个主意。
[whispering]
（低语）
- Hey.
嘿。
Did you hear what happened at the joust last year?
你听说去年马上比武发生了什么吗？
It was a bloodbath.
那简直就是一场大屠杀。
Heads literally rolled.
头颅真的在地上滚。
- It's true.
这是真的。
My brother was there.
我哥哥当时在场。
A part of him still is.
他的一部分至今还在那里。
- Now it's time to get jousty.
现在该去比武了。
[trumpet fanfare]
[号角声]
- You know, if there was a show-off contest,
你知道吗，如果有炫耀比赛，
you'd be the Queen of that too.
你也会是那里的女王。
- [scoffs] That's not showing off.
这不算炫耀。
This is showing off.
这才是炫耀。
[jazz trumpet solo]
[爵士小号独奏]
- Are you done, Anne?
- 安妮，你完了吗？
- ♪ A-squee-bah, a-squee-bah ♪
- ♪ 阿斯奎巴，阿斯奎巴 ♪
♪ A-squee-squal-ee-squee, lah-bee-bah-bah-dah ♪
♪ 阿斯奎斯奎利斯奎，拉比巴巴达 ♪
- Okay, okay. We all get it, you can scat.
- 好了，好了。我们都知道你会即兴演唱。
Welcome to the Royal Jousting Tournament!
欢迎来到皇家马上比武大赛！
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
- Jousting in today's first round
- 今天第一轮的马上比武
will be Sirs Nicky, Ricky, Dicky, and...
将是尼基爵士、瑞奇爵士、迪基爵士和...
Wait, that's it? Those are the only contestants?
等等，就这样？只有这些参赛者？
- It worked. We're the only contestants.
- 成功了。我们是仅有的参赛者。
Now one of us is guaranteed to win,
现在我们中肯定有一个人会赢，
so you two fall down. - But why should I fall down?
所以你们两个倒下。 - 但我为什么要倒下？
You and Ricky should fall down.
你和Ricky应该倒下。
- Sir Ricky falls down for no one.
- Ricky爵士不会为任何人倒下。
- Two of us are gonna have to fall down if we wanna beat Dawn.
- 如果我们想打败Dawn，我们中的两个人得倒下。
- You're all falling down...
- 你们都会倒下...
[imitates horse chuffing]
[模仿马的喷气声]
And none of you are going to beat me.
而你们谁也赢不了我。
- We have a last-minute addition.
- 我们有一个最后一刻的加入者。
Joining the joust will be Dame Dawn.
参加马上比武的是女骑士Dawn。
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
- To your corners!
- 各就各位！
[dramatic music]
[戏剧性音乐]
♪ ♪
Let the joust begin.
开始比武。
[cheers and applause]
[欢呼和掌声]
♪ ♪
- [imitates horse chuffing]
- [模仿马的喷气声]
[scattered screams]
[零星的尖叫声]
[confused murmuring]
[困惑的低语声]
- Well, it looks like for the first time ever,
- 好吧，看起来这是有史以来第一次，
we have a tie.
我们打成了平手。
- No! One of us has to be the winner,
- 不！我们中必须有一个是赢家，
and hold the fair maiden's hand.
并且牵起那位美丽少女的手。
- Knight Nicky's got this.
- 骑士尼基能做到。
- No, Knight Ricky does.
- 不，骑士里基能做到。
- No, Knight Dicky does.
- 不，骑士迪基能做到。
- None of you are knights.
- 你们都不是真正的骑士。
It's only the Dame who has game.
只有女爵才有真本事。
- Just fight already!
— 快开打吧！
- It's called Get Jousty, not Get Talky.
— 这是《决斗吧》，不是《聊天吧》。
[all booing]
【众人嘘声】
- That's it! This is my advantage.
— 就这样！这是我的优势。
- Every Quad for himself.
— 各自为战。
♪ ♪
- Fighting with turkey legs? Genius!
— 用火鸡腿打架？天才！
Ow--uh, yes, d--don't do that.
哎哟——呃，对，别——别那样做。
It's a waste of food.
那是浪费食物。
- Wait, he's right.
— 等等，他说得对。
First one to finish their turkey leg wins.
第一个吃完火鸡腿的人获胜。
♪ ♪
- Kids! Kids, wait! What--what are you doing?
- 孩子们！孩子们，等等！你们在做什么？
- Look at us. We're eating turkey legs
- 看看我们。我们在吃火鸡腿
to prove who's most mature.
来证明谁最成熟。
- But why are you trying to prove who's most mature?
- 但你们为什么要证明谁最成熟呢？
- Well, Dawn got a date, and then we wanted to see
- 嗯，Dawn有了约会，然后我们想看看
who could complete the triangle of romance first.
谁能先完成浪漫三角。
- The triangle of what?
- 浪漫三角是什么？
- You know, connect with your date;
- 你知道，和你的约会对象连接；
hold hands; look in the eyes; mind, body, soul.
牵手；凝视对方；心灵、身体、灵魂。
- That's why you guys have been acting so weird?
这就是你们表现得这么奇怪的原因？
- That's why I've been wearing this armor all day?
这就是我一整天都穿着这身盔甲的原因？
I've lost 12 pounds.
我已经瘦了12磅。
- I don't think the triangle of romance is even a thing.
我不认为浪漫三角关系是个真实存在的东西。
- Yeah, who would tell you something so dumb?
是啊，谁会告诉你这么愚蠢的事情？
- [laughs nervously]
[紧张地笑]
Dooley the Great bids you adieu.
伟大的杜利向你告别。
Poof!
砰！
- Mack, I'm sorry I ruined our day.
麦克，对不起我毁了我们的日子。
I--I guess I just wasn't ready for a date.
我想我只是还没准备好约会。
I mean, that's why I dragged Mae and Miles along.
我的意思是，这就是为什么我拉上了Mae和Miles一起。
- And we're sorry too.
我们也很抱歉。
- I--I guess we're not as mature as we thought.
我想我们并不像我们想象的那样成熟。
- Well, I think admitting that is pretty mature.
嗯，我认为承认这一点已经很成熟了。
And don't worry, when it's time to date, you'll know it.
别担心，当约会的时候到了，你会知道的。
- And kids, you can't force a connection.
孩子们，你们不能强迫建立联系。
That happens naturally after you get to know someone.
那是在你了解某人之后自然发生的。
Kinda like that.
有点像那样。
- You know, dates are cool,
你知道，约会是很酷的，
but that joust looked like way more fun.
但那个比武看起来更有趣多了。
- Yeah, I kinda wanted to join in.
- 是啊，我有点想参加。
- [giggles]
- [咯咯笑]
- Oh. - Okay, okay.
- 哦。 - 好吧，好吧。
All right, right-- Ah! Right, everybody,
好吧，对——啊！对，各位，
everybody, everybody, hey! Just--just scat.
各位，各位，嘿！就——就散开。
[all scatting]
[所有人散开]
- You're loving this, aren't ya?
- 你很享受这个，不是吗？
- ♪ Oh, yeah ♪
- ♪ 哦，是的 ♪
[all continue scatting]
[所有人继续散开]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ 呐，呐，呐，呐，呐，呐 ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
[口哨声]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪